

Profile

A industrial engineer passionate for technologies currently dedicated to grown on coding field like junior front end developer with 7 months of professional experience actively look for new opportunities to learn and apply my knowledge.

Employment History

Software Developer Junior, Celerik S.A., Barranquilla

OCTOBER 2021 - MARCH 2022

- Create small features and update views functionalities.
- Create interfaces templates using React.js.
- Add CSS styles to new view templates.
- Help to review pre-existing interfaces and analyze which components we can reuse.

QA Analyst Junior, Celerik S.A., Barranquilla

MARCH 2022 - APRIL 2022

- Create automated tests for websites using the webdriver.io framework.
- Help review user experience on website navigation.
- Actively learning about code quality testing.

Education

Industrial Enginieer, Universidad de la costa CUC, Barranquilla

JULY 2013 - FEBRUARY 2019

Details

3022523666

heidyprimo10@outlook.com

Skills

React

Node.js

HTML

CSS

Git

JavaScript